Do you play much sport?
Not really.
I occasionally watch the rugby on TV ...
...but I'm not a big sports fan.
Did you see the match at the weekend?
Oh, not sport again!
So, have you got any exciting plans for next week?
Well, er...
No, not really.
Just work.
I've got a lot to do in the shop this week...
...because we're going to a wedding next weekend.
Oh, the shop? What do you do?
I'm a florist.
What a great job! Where's the shop?
Not far from here. I'll show you some time.
That would be great!
And are you the manager, or...
Well, not really...
...it's my shop.
Wow. That's amazing!
So you're a businesswoman!
Do you work on your own?
No, I have someone to help.
Tina. She comes in for a few hours every day.
Oh, that's good.
How about you? What do you do?
Oh, marketing. Boring!
Same as Mark...
He works in marketing.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I find it boring.
Do you have any plans for the weekend?
Actually, yes. I'm going to visit my brother, Dan.
Oh, I remember Dan. How is he?
He's fine. He's married now.
To Martina.
Anyway, we really must go.
I need to get back to the shop.
Yeah, of course.
It was really nice to meet you.
Yeah, you too.
Nice to meet you, Mark.
It was great to see you again, Annie.
Yeah! We must meet up soon!
Definitely!
Actually...
...it's Leo's birthday in a couple of weeks.
Perhaps we could meet then.
OK, great. I'll give you a call.
And say hello to Dan for me!